<resources>
    <string name="app_name">გარემოს სიახლეები</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">გამარჯობა ცარიელი ფრაგმენტი</string>
    <string name="ecology">ეკოლოგია</string>
    <string name="tips_for_preserving_the_ecology_of_the_environment">რჩევები გარემოს ეკოლოგიის შესანარჩუნებლად</string>
    <string name="next">შემდეგი</string>
    <string name="read_the_tips_and_help_make_the_environment_more_environmentally_friendly">წაიკითხეთ რჩევები და დაეხმარეთ გარემოს უფრო ეკოლოგიურად გახადონ</string>
    <string name="home">სახლი</string>
    <string name="save">Გადარჩენა</string>
    <string name="featured_tips">გამორჩეული რჩევები</string>
    <string name="popular_tips">პოპულარული რჩევები</string>
    <string name="more_news">მეტი სიახლე</string>

    <!--Featured Tips-->
    <string name="featured_title1">თანამედროვე მეურნეობის მცენარეები</string>
    <string name="featured_temp1">32 ° C</string>
    <string name="featured_weather1">მსუბუქი წვიმა</string>
    <string name="featured_water1">85%</string>
    <string name="featured_description1">Various types of modern farming methods used nowadays include agribusiness and intensive farming techniques. These methods have significantly contributed to increasing farming productivity.

Another important aspect of modern farming technology is the ability to regulate weather conditions within closed environments, such as greenhouses. This allows farmers to create optimal growing conditions for crops regardless of external weather conditions.

Additionally, advanced farming technology also includes the use of specialized tools and equipment for measuring moisture levels in the soil. Accurate moisture measurement helps farmers efficiently manage irrigation and ensure proper hydration for their crops.

Overall, the development of agriculture and farming technology has revolutionized the way farming is conducted, leading to higher productivity, improved efficiency, and more sustainable practices.</string>

    <string name="featured_title2">Outomatic გადამუშავება</string>
    <string name="featured_temp2">20 ° C</string>
    <string name="featured_weather2">მსუბუქი წვიმა</string>
    <string name="featured_water2">80%</string>
    <string name="featured_description2">Automatic recycling is a revolutionary concept that aims to streamline and simplify the recycling process. With traditional recycling methods, individuals are responsible for sorting their waste into different categories, such as paper, plastic, and glass. However, automatic recycling takes this burden off our shoulders and replaces it with intelligent technology.

The first step in automatic recycling is the use of smart bins. These bins are equipped with sensors that can detect the type of waste being disposed of. For example, if you throw away a plastic bottle, the sensor will identify it as plastic waste. This technology eliminates the need for manual sorting, saving time and effort.

Once the waste is identified, the smart bins automatically separate the different types of materials. This is done using mechanical separators and conveyor belts. The plastic waste is separated from the paper waste, and the glass waste is separated from the metal waste, all without any human intervention. This automated process ensures that each type of waste is properly sorted and can be recycled efficiently.

After the waste is sorted, it is sent to recycling facilities where it undergoes further processing. The automatic recycling system ensures that the waste is clean and free from contaminants, which improves the quality of the recycled materials. This technology also enables a higher recycling rate, as more materials can be efficiently processed and reused.

In conclusion, automatic recycling is a game-changer in the world of waste management. It simplifies the recycling process, reduces the burden on individuals, and improves the efficiency of recycling facilities. With this technology, we can move towards a more sustainable future, where recycling is not only easy but also highly effective in reducing our environmental footprint.</string>

    <string name="featured_title3">სიყვარული მცენარის მინიჭება</string>
    <string name="featured_temp3">26 ° C</string>
    <string name="featured_weather3">მსუბუქი წვიმა</string>
    <string name="featured_water3">89%</string>
    <string name="featured_description3">Love Identify Plant is a fascinating app that has revolutionized the way we interact with nature. With just a few clicks, this app can identify any plant species, making it a valuable tool for both amateur and professional botanists.

Gone are the days of flipping through guidebooks or consulting experts to identify a plant. Love Identify Plant uses advanced image recognition technology to analyze a photo of the plant and provide accurate information about its species, habitat, and care instructions. This app has made plant identification accessible to everyone, regardless of their level of expertise.

Using Love Identify Plant is incredibly simple. All you need to do is take a clear photo of the plant you want to identify and upload it to the app. Within seconds, the app will analyze the image and provide you with a detailed description of the plant. It can identify a wide range of species, from common garden plants to rare and exotic ones.

Not only does Love Identify Plant help with identification, but it also serves as an educational tool. The app provides users with interesting facts and trivia about each plant species, helping to deepen their understanding and appreciation for the natural world. It also offers tips on how to care for and cultivate different plants, making it a valuable resource for gardening enthusiasts.

In conclusion, Love Identify Plant has revolutionized the way we engage with plants. This app has made plant identification accessible to everyone, and its educational features make it an invaluable tool for nature lovers. Whether you\'re a professional botanist or simply curious about the plants around you, Love Identify Plant is a must-have app that will enrich your understanding of the natural world.</string>
    <!--Featured Tips-->

    <!--Popular Tips-->
    <string name="popular_title">ნარჩენების მართვა: გარემოსდაცვითი ჯანმრთელობის ზრუნვა</string>
    <string name="popular_desc">Waste management is a crucial aspect of caring for environmental health. As the world\'s population continues to grow and consumption rates increase, proper waste management becomes even more important. It involves the collection, transportation, processing, and disposal of waste materials in a way that minimizes their impact on the environment.

One of the key goals of waste management is to reduce the amount of waste generated. This can be achieved through various strategies, such as promoting recycling and composting. Recycling allows materials such as paper, plastic, glass, and metal to be reused, reducing the need for raw materials and decreasing the energy required for manufacturing. Composting, on the other hand, involves the decomposition of organic waste into nutrient-rich soil, which can be used for gardening and agriculture.\n

Proper waste disposal is another crucial aspect of waste management. Landfills are commonly used for disposing of non-recyclable and non-compostable waste. However, modern waste management practices aim to minimize the use of landfills and instead focus on alternative methods such as waste-to-energy plants. These plants convert waste into energy through processes like incineration or anaerobic digestion, reducing the volume of waste and generating electricity or heat in the process.

Waste management also involves the safe handling and treatment of hazardous waste. Hazardous waste includes materials that are toxic, flammable, corrosive, or reactive. Improper disposal of hazardous waste can have severe consequences on human health and the environment. Therefore, it is crucial to have proper regulations and systems in place to ensure its safe collection, transportation, and treatment.\n

In addition to reducing waste generation and proper disposal, waste management also involves raising awareness and educating the public about the importance of responsible waste management practices. Encouraging individuals to reduce, reuse, and recycle can significantly contribute to preserving the environment and maintaining its health for future generations.

In conclusion, waste management plays a vital role in caring for environmental health. By implementing effective waste management practices, we can reduce the impact of waste on the environment, conserve resources, and promote a sustainable future. It is a collective responsibility, and by working together, we can make a significant difference in preserving our planet for generations to come.</string>
    <!--Popular Tips-->

    <!--More New-->
    <string name="new_title1">დარგვის ხე: დარგე ერთი ხე მილიონი სარგებლით</string>
    <string name="new_desc1">Trees are living creatures that play an important role in our lives and the environment. Planting a tree is not only an act of caring for nature, but also an investment in the future. One planted tree can bring us many benefits that extend far beyond its physical form.\n

One of the main arguments in favor of planting trees is their ability of oxygen formation. Trees absorb carbon dioxide and release oxygen, which makes them indispensable for maintaining balance in the atmosphere. They are natural filters that improve the quality of the air we breathe. Thanks to trees, the level of air pollution can be reduced, which has a positive effect on the health of people and animals.\n

Trees also play an important role in climate regulation. They create natural barriers from strong winds and protect from the negative effects of sunlight. In addition, they help to conserve water in the soil and prevent erosion. Trees also contribute to the cooling of the environment, which is especially important in urban areas where temperatures can be higher due to urban heat.

In addition to environmental benefits, trees also offer economic benefits. Growing trees improve the appearance of the environment and increase the value of real estate. Studies show that the presence of green spaces around a home or workplace can increase its value and attractiveness to buyers or tenants. In addition, trees create shade and help reduce air conditioning costs during the hot summer months.\n

But planting trees is not only the responsibility of the state or organizations, it is an action that each of us can perform. Even one planted tree can have a huge impact on the environment and our lives. We can start by planting a tree in our garden, on a plot or even on a balcony. Each tree has the potential to bring a million benefits, including air improvement, climate regulation and economic benefits.

So let\'s turn our planet into a greener and healthier place to live together. Plant a tree and get a million benefits!</string>

    <string name="new_title2">ქარხანა 2022: გადამუშავების ადგილის ქარხანა მალანგში</string>
    <string name="new_desc2">The Factory 2022: Recycling Place Factory in Malang is an innovative project that aims to tackle the growing problem of waste management in Indonesia. Located in the city of Malang, this factory is set to become a hub for recycling and sustainable practices, making a significant impact on the environment and the local community.

The factory is equipped with state-of-the-art recycling technology that can process various types of waste, including plastic, paper, glass, and metal. This advanced machinery ensures that the waste is properly sorted, cleaned, and transformed into reusable materials. By recycling these materials, the factory reduces the amount of waste that ends up in landfills, helping to alleviate the strain on the environment.

One of the unique aspects of the Factory 2022 is its focus on community involvement. The factory actively encourages local residents to participate in recycling initiatives by providing education and training programs. This not only raises awareness about the importance of recycling but also creates employment opportunities for the community. By engaging and empowering the local population, the factory aims to create a sustainable and self-sufficient recycling ecosystem.

In addition to recycling, the Factory 2022 also promotes the use of renewable energy sources. Solar panels and wind turbines have been installed on the factory premises to generate clean and sustainable energy. This reduces the factory\'s reliance on fossil fuels, further minimizing its carbon footprint and contributing to a greener future.

Overall, the Factory 2022: Recycling Place Factory in Malang is a commendable initiative that demonstrates the potential for sustainable waste management practices. By combining advanced recycling technology, community involvement, and renewable energy sources, this factory sets a positive example for other industries and communities. It is a step towards a more sustainable future, where waste is seen as a valuable resource rather than a burden on the environment.</string>
    <string name="new_title3">შეამცირეთ დაბინძურება დედამიწაზე ჩვენს გარშემო ხეების დარგვით</string>
    <string name="new_desc3">Planting trees is a simple yet powerful way to reduce pollution on Earth and improve the overall health of our planet. Trees play a crucial role in absorbing carbon dioxide, a major greenhouse gas responsible for climate change. By planting trees around us, we can help mitigate the effects of pollution and create a healthier environment for future generations.

One of the main benefits of trees is their ability to absorb carbon dioxide and release oxygen through the process of photosynthesis. This helps to reduce the levels of greenhouse gases in the atmosphere, which in turn helps to combat climate change. Trees also act as natural air filters, trapping pollutants such as nitrogen dioxide, sulfur dioxide, and particulate matter. By planting trees in urban areas, we can significantly improve air quality and reduce the harmful effects of pollution on human health.

In addition to their air-cleansing properties, trees also play a vital role in preventing soil erosion and water pollution. The roots of trees help to stabilize the soil, preventing it from being washed away by rainwater and reducing the risk of landslides. Furthermore, trees act as natural water filters, absorbing pollutants and excess nutrients from the soil, thus preventing them from entering water bodies such as rivers and lakes.

Planting trees also has numerous social and economic benefits. Trees provide shade, reducing the need for air conditioning and lowering energy costs. They also create a more pleasant and inviting environment, which can have a positive impact on mental health and well-being. Additionally, trees contribute to the overall beauty and aesthetics of an area, attracting tourists and boosting local economies.

In conclusion, planting trees is a simple yet effective way to reduce pollution on Earth. By absorbing carbon dioxide, filtering the air, preventing soil erosion, and improving water quality, trees play a crucial role in creating a healthier and more sustainable planet. It is essential for individuals, communities, and governments to recognize the importance of tree planting and take action to preserve and expand our green spaces. Together, we can make a significant impact on reducing pollution and ensuring a better future for generations to come.</string>
    <!--More New-->

    <string name="tips_you_can_return_to_at_any_time">რჩევები შეგიძლიათ ნებისმიერ დროს დაუბრუნდეთ</string>
    <string name="detail">დეტალი</string>
    <string name="temperature">ტემპერატურა</string>
    <string name="water">მორწყვა</string>
    <string name="weather">ამინდი</string>
    <string name="description">აღწერილობა</string>
</resources>